Britta Rodenbeck

Web developer

INFO

- rodenbeck.britta@gmail.com
- (815) 222-8436
- brittarodenbeck.com
- github.com/brodenbeck
- linkedin.com/brittarodenbeck

EDUCATION

Front End Bootcamp, Grand Circus Detroit, June 2016

Bachelor of Psychological Sciences, Northern Illinois University, December 2014

SKILLS

- CSS, Sass, Stylus
- JavaScript, Vue.js, jQuery, React,
 Angular 1.x
- Git, GitHub, Bitbucket
- Webpack, Gulp
- PHP, Laravel
- NPM, Yarn, Composer
- VSCode, PHPStorm, Sublime, Atom
- Adobe Photoshop, Zeplin, Figma,
 Adobe Illustrator

PROFILE-

I am a web developer specializing in front-end development and design, experienced with all stages of the development cycle from product conception to design, development, testing, deployment, and maintenance. I have a passion for engaging and beautiful UI with practical UX.

EXPERIENCE-

UI Engineer

Career Now Brands, September 2017 - February 2018

Collaborating with lead developer and design / product teams to implement front-end solutions and builds for 20+ web properties and applications with a focus on user interface and user experience using Vue.js. Using Asana and GitHub to self-manage productivity on projects for optimal workflow to meet strict deadlines. Executing quality assurance tests on products using Karma and Jasmine.

Web Developer

Career Now Brands, July 2016 - September 2017

Responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining 20+ web applications and properties. Lead a team to complete end-to-end design and development for web property responsible for matching prospective students with CDL training facilities nationwide. Collaborated with Paid Media team to execute A / B testing on pay-per-click social media outreach campaigns.

Teaching Assistant

Grand Circus Detroit, June 2016 - February 2017
Aided the classroom teacher of several HTML and CSS courses for adults with curriculum planning, student assistance, and project evaluation.